Don Alfons Nisnoni Resume

PERSONAL DATA



Date of Birth: 18 September 1995 (26 years old)

Address: Rata Kuta Street 107 No. 4 KUTA, KAB. BADUNG, BALI, ID 80361

Phone: +6283809705594

Preffered Position: Front-end Web Developer

Email: <u>donalfonsnnisnoni@gmail.com</u>

Website: donnisnoni.github.io

GitHub: donnisnoni LinkedIn: donnisnoni

SUMMARY

Hello!

My name is Don Alfons Nisnoni. I'm a passionate, motivated, and creative web developer with 2 years of experience. Mostly focused on front-end, but has the flexibility and experience to work on back-end as well. Experienced with NodeJS, VueJS, ReactJS, PHP, and testing.

I am very enthusiastic and always eager to learn more about technology especially web development both front-end and back-end. I always look forward to building things and products with it.

EDUCATION

Diploma Degree of Computer Science @ <u>STIKOM</u> <u>UYELINDO Kupang</u>

Jul 2015 - Dec 2019 - **GPA: 3.44** - Graduated on Nov 2020 due COVID-19

SKILLS

Thing's that I've touch so far:

Software/Tools:

Git, GitHub, Docker, Netlify, Vercel, PostCSS, Hugo SSG, Discourse

Databases:

Redis, MySQL & MariaDB

Programming Languages:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, Typescript, C#, V, SASS, SQL, PHP, Python

Frameworks/Libraries:

jQuery, Vue, React, Svelte, Sapper, Codelgniter, Laravel, Express, Fastify, Sequelize, TailwindCSS

Technique:

Responsive Web Design, a11y, i18n, PWA

EXPERIENCES

Web Developer & IT Support

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

- Build a website for improve student's online services
- Upgrade & improve campus main website
- Create work email for lecturer's
- Analyze and improve existing campus websites security and UI
- Upgrade campus tech stacks

Part-time Front-End Web Developer

Feb 2021 - May 2021 @ Vlingo

• Implementing <u>vlingo/auth</u> UI using SvelteKit framework

Full-time Front-End Web Developer

May 2021 - Present @ Bali Casa Villas

- Maintain NuxtJS and VueJS websites
- Maintain Laravel websites
- Extending a discourse forum (Develop discourse widgets and extensions)
- Develop JupyterLab extensions